import { QuizInfo } from "./Types";

export const MockData: QuizInfo[] = [
  {
    question: "What year did Radiohead release their album 'OK Computer'?",
    answers: ["1997", "1995", "1999"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which band is known for their hit song 'Smells Like Teen Spirit'?",
    answers: ["Nirvana", "Pearl Jam", "Soundgarden"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "Which band's debut album is 'Is This It'?",
    answers: ["The Strokes", "Interpol", "The White Stripes"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "Which band's lead singer is Win Butler?",
    answers: ["Arcade Fire", "The National", "Fleet Foxes"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the debut album of Vampire Weekend called?",
    answers: ["Vampire Weekend", "Contra", "Modern Vampires of the City"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which band's song 'I Will Follow You into the Dark' gained popularity?",
    answers: ["Death Cab for Cutie", "Modest Mouse", "Bright Eyes"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "Which band released the album 'Veckatimest'?",
    answers: ["Grizzly Bear", "Fleet Foxes", "Animal Collective"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of the first studio album by Tame Impala?",
    answers: ["Innerspeaker", "Lonerism", "Currents"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "Which band's album 'Boxer' features the song 'Fake Empire'?",
    answers: ["The National", "Fleet Foxes", "Bon Iver"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of the lead singer of The Shins?",
    answers: ["James Mercer", "Ben Gibbard", "Sam Beam"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "Which band released the album 'Teen Dream'?",
    answers: ["Beach House", "Real Estate", "Deerhunter"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "What genre is associated with the band Spoon?",
    answers: ["Indie rock", "Post-punk revival", "Shoegaze"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which band's debut album is 'We Have the Facts and We're Voting Yes'?",
    answers: ["Death Cab for Cutie", "Interpol", "The Antlers"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of the lead singer of Fleet Foxes?",
    answers: ["Robin Pecknold", "Ben Bridwell", "Wayne Coyne"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "Which band released the album 'Attack on Memory'?",
    answers: ["Cloud Nothings", "Wavves", "The Men"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of the first studio album by Sufjan Stevens?",
    answers: ["A Sun Came", "Michigan", "Seven Swans"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
];
